A father and a daughter, divided by a case, endangered by the truth.
Class Action is a drama, crime, history film directed by Michael Apted.
A liberal activist lawyer alienated his daughter Maggie
years ago when she discovered his many affairs.
Now a conservative corporate lawyer, Maggie agrees to
go up against her father in court.
To gain promotion, she must defend an auto manufacturer against charges
that their explosion-prone station wagons are unsafe.
As her mother begs for peace, Maggie takes on her dad in a
trial that turns increasingly personal and nasty.
Jedediah Tucker Ward, played by Gene Hackman.
Maggie Ward, played by Mary Elizabeth Mastrantonio.
Michael Grazier, played by Colin Friels.
Estelle Ward, played by Joanna Merlin.
Nick Holbrook, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Quinn, played by Donald Moffat.
Class Action is a 1991 American legal drama film directed by Michael Apted.
Gene Hackman and Mary Elizabeth Mastrantonio star; Laurence Fishburne, Colin
Friels, Fred Dalton Thompson, and Donald Moffat are also featured.
The film was entered into the 17th Moscow International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of lawyer, courtroom, auto industry,
father daughter conflict, estranged daughter.
The tone is emotional.